reaxxion.com 2017-12-09

# Privacy Policy

Reaxxion is owned and operated by Kinds Media LLC (“we” “our” or “us”). This document is to inform you how information about you is collected, used, and shared with others. We also want you to know about the choices you have when you visit us at http://www.reaxxion.com (the “Site”). If you have questions or comments about this policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Information We Collect

When you visit our Site, send us or a Site writer an email, submit or comment on an article, or otherwise communicate with us or a Site writer, we may collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us or a Site writer.  We may also collect personal information from third parties, including without limitation, our business partners.  Personal information is information through which you can be identified such as your name, email address, photograph, and telephone number.

If you engage with our Site content through third-party social networking sites, we may have access to certain information associated with your social media account such as your name, email address, photograph, birthday, location, and people you follow or like.   For information on controlling access to your personal information through social networking sites, you should review their privacy policies and terms of use.

We may use (or authorize third parties to use) web beacons, cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies (“Tracking Technologies”) at our Site to collect information about you, your online behavior, your computer, or your mobile device.  Such information may include, without limitation, the type of browser and operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your geographic location, the pages you visit, how long you visit each page, the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, etc.  You can change some of your privacy preferences through your browser.  For example, you can delete browser cookies from your computer or set your browser to reject browser cookies.  However, doing so may limit some functionalities of our Site.  Also, blocking or deleting browser cookies may not block or delete other types of cookies including flash cookies.    For additional information about browser privacy preferences, please consult the “Help” section of your browser.

#### Use of Information We Collect

We may use the information we collect for our own marketing and non-marketing purposes.  For example, your personal information (like email address) may be used to alert you to upcoming articles, features, or events.  We may also share your personal information and information collected through Tracking Technologies with third parties in the United States and other jurisdictions for marketing and non-marketing purposes.

We currently do not share or transfer your personal information and information collected through Tracking Technologies to other companies.

#### Information Collected by Third Parties

Some content on our Site may be sponsored by or co-branded with third parties who may obtain personal information from you if you voluntarily participate in sponsored or co-branded activities such as sweepstakes and promotions.  We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of such third parties.  Therefore, you should review their privacy practices carefully before participating or providing personal information to such third parties.

Third parties may also serve advertisements and use Tracking Technologies to collect information about you and your activities at our Site such as the links you click, the advertisements you see and click, the categories of search terms you enter, etc.  These companies may use the information collected at our Site and other websites for a variety of purposes including analytics and providing advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  This type of advertising customization is sometimes referred to as “online behavioral” or “interest-based” advertising.  For more information about Tracking Technologies please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/faqs.asp.  Please note that the use of Tracking Technologies by third parties at our Site is subject to their own privacy policies, not our privacy policy.

You can obtain information about your choices concerning online behavioral advertising including how you can opt-out of some uses of information collected by members of the Network Advertising Initiative that may serve advertisements at our Site by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

#### Links to other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of other websites.  For example, if you click on an advertisement that links to another website, this privacy policy will not apply to information collected at that other website.  We recommend that you review the privacy policies of other websites before you visit those websites or provide any personal information.

#### Posting Comments

You can post your own comments and other information at our Site (“Comments”) through our comments platform, which is run by Disqus.   Comments posted at our Site are subject to our privacy policy and the privacy policy of Disqus at http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/.   Because our Site receives significant traffic and is accessible to anyone on the Internet, you should not post Comments that are private or that you do not want to be used and viewed by others.   You are solely responsible for any legal or other repercussions that occur as a result of Comments you post at our Site.  We assume no responsibility or liability which may arise from your Comments.

#### Security

We have implemented administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of personal information in our custody or control.  However, we cannot guarantee that these safeguards will prevent the unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your personal information.

#### Persons Under 18

Our Site is not intended for persons under 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under 18.  If you are the parent or guardian of a person under 18 and believe that he or she has provided personal information to us, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Visitors Outside of the United States

Our business is located in the United States, which may not offer a level of privacy protection as great as that offered in other jurisdictions. We make no representation that the practices described in this privacy policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States.  Any information that you provide to us may be transferred to and processed in the United States.  By using this Site, you consent to your information being collected, used, and transferred as disclosed herein.

#### Revisions to this Privacy Policy

We may revise this privacy policy from time-to-time in our sole discretion.  Please visit this Site and review our privacy policy periodically for changes.  By continuing to access or use our Site after changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the terms of the revised privacy policy.

Effective:  November 10, 2014

Nov 1, 2014
